vps.ag 2018-09-12

# VPS.AG - Terms and conditions

### PRIVACY POLICY

Your privacy is important to Belcloud Hosting Corporation (“Belcloud”), therefore Belcloud takes great care in handling the personal data of its customers in order to protect customer privacy. Belcloud believes you should know what information they collect from you, as well as how that information is used, disclosed, and protected. Belcloud has created this Privacy Statement to explain their privacy practices and policies. This statement does not cover data hosted, transmitted or processed on infrastructure leased from Belcloud by its customers. The customer leasing Belcloud services will be responsible for the personal data processing, acting as a data controller. If at any time Belcloud has access to personal data stored on infrastructure leased from Belcloud, Belcloud shall be the data processor, and any actions performed by Belcloud in relation to such data shall be solely governed by the agreement concluded between Belcloud’s customer and Belcloud.

Belcloud will not sell or disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent except as otherwise provided in this statement or our General Terms and Conditions of Sale and Services, and Acceptable Use Policy.

By using Belcloud websites, products and services you agree and give consent to the terms set out in this Privacy Statement.

This Privacy Statement was most recently changed on 24th of May 2018.

#### **Belcloud MAY COLLECT YOUR DATA WHEN**

  * You order a product or service from Belcloud;
  * You participate in a Belcloud survey;
  * You subscribe to a Belcloud newsletter;
  * You ask Belcloud for information about a Belcloud service, or contact Belcloud with a question, comment or complaint;
  * You submit an abuse notification to Belcloud.

In addition, Belcloud may collect data about you from fraud‐prevention agencies, referral partners, business directories and credit reference agencies.

Belcloud does not intentionally collect information from children under the age of 16.

#### **Belcloud MAY COLLECT THE FOLLOWING DATA ABOUT YOU**

  * Your name, (business/private) address, phone number, date of birth, email address, personal identification numbers (including but limited to social security number), documents and information that certify your identity; 
  * Your Belcloud account information – such as Belcloud products and services you ordered, your customer ID, service charges, and the use of Belcloud services; 
  * Your IP address when placing an online order through Belcloud’s website. At the moment of securely entering your personal details and payment information; 
  * Your contact with Belcloud – such as a note or recording of a call you make to Belcloud, a chat record when you engage in a chat session with Belcloud, an email or letter you send to Belcloud or other records of any contact you have with Belcloud; 
  * Information about your payment methods, such as credit card number, bank account number or other banking information;
  * Information provided by you to Belcloud when you notify Belcloud of a (suspected) breach of Belcloud’s Acceptable Use Policy;

#### **PAYMENT INFORMATION**

Your payment transaction may be processed by one of our third-party payment vendors, ex: PayPal, CoinPayments, SafeCharge etc. These vendors are payment providers who can process your payment on behalf of Belcloud.

#### **Belcloud MAY SHARE DATA ABOUT YOU WITH**

  * Partners or agents involved in delivering the services you’ve ordered with Belcloud;
  * Debt collection agencies or other debt recovery organizations;
  * Law enforcement agencies, regulatory organizations, courts or other public authorities to the extent required by law;
  * A Belcloud customer, if you notify Belcloud that this customer use of Belcloud services violates the Belcloud’s Acceptable Use Policy or applicable law; 
  * A third party that has claimed that your use of the Belcloud services violates the Belcloud’s Acceptable Use Policy or applicable law (to the extent such sharing is required by law). 

#### **Belcloud MAY PROCESS YOUR DATA FOR THE FOLLOWING PURPOSES:**

  * Partners or agents involved in delivering the services you’ve ordered with Belcloud;
  * Debt collection agencies or other debt recovery organizations;
  * Law enforcement agencies, regulatory organizations, courts or other public authorities to the extent required by law;
  * A Belcloud customer, if you notify Belcloud that this customer use of Belcloud services violates the Belcloud’s Acceptable Use Policy or applicable law; 
  * A third party that has claimed that your use of the Belcloud services violates the Belcloud’s Acceptable Use Policy or applicable law (to the extent such sharing is required by law). 

#### **Belcloud MAY PROCESS YOUR DATA FOR THE FOLLOWING PURPOSES:**

  * Processing of orders and provision of products and services;
  * Conducting market research, conducting retention and customer satisfaction surveys, conducting marketing (including social media) and sales activities; 
  * Communicating with customers to provide information about services of Belcloud and affiliated companies, to provide information about offers, orders, provision of services, order status and payment, to provide support and maintenance services, to handle complaints, and to answer questions from (potential) customers; 
  * Performing financial processes (including calculating, invoicing and collection of service charges), processing financial transactions regarding the acceptance of orders, checking solvency and granting debt collection rights to third parties; 
  * Investigating and processing suspected violations of Belcloud’s Acceptable Use Policy;
  * Ensuring the security of persons, goods, objects, and performing fraud detection;
  * Conducting legal processes, including conducting legal proceedings, and collecting evidence for civil legal proceedings;
  * Complying with statutory obligations, including the provision of data to authorized authorities in the context of criminal investigations, complying with (applicable) data retention obligations, and the provision to third parties of data concerning customers in connection with an infringement of these third parties’ rights. 

#### **COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**

A cookie is a small amount of information that our websites can store on your computer or any other device used. Your device provides this cookie when visiting the same website in the future. Cookies are used to enhance your experience with a website.

Belcloud uses cookies to identify visitors and track visits to their websites, store login session information and remember your user preferences.

Visitors can disable the storage of cookies in their web browser, but should be aware that doing so may affect the quality of the experience with a website.

#### **WHERE DOES Belcloud STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

Personal data collected by Belcloud is stored and processed in a data center in Sofia, Bulgaria, being its primary and only location. Personal data collected by affiliates, service providers or payment providers of Belcloud may be stored and processed in any other country where they maintain facilities.

#### **HOW TO ACCESS AND CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

You can view and edit part of your personally identifiable information by logging into the Profile Area of this website. 

If you cannot access certain personal data collected by Belcloud via the link above or directly through the Belcloud services you use, you can always contact Belcloud using the contact details listed below this statement. Belcloud will respond to requests to access (make available) or delete your personal data within 5 business days.

You can choose whether you do not wish to receive promotional communications from Belcloud by email, physical mail and telephone, or marketing communications (e.g., news and updates) from Belcloud. You can exercise that right at any time by contacting admin[at]belcloud[dot]net.

#### **SECURITY AND SAFETY FEATURES**

Belcloud is committed to protecting the security of your personal data. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to enable protecting your personal data from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. E.g., we store the personal data you provide on computer systems that have limited access and are in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential data (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption.

Belcloud is ISO/IEC 27001:2013 certified for Information Security Management and compliant with Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS). These certifications help Belcloud ensure that they have enterprise- grade controls in place to protect customer information and payment data.

#### **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Belcloud will update this Privacy Statement when necessary to reflect customer feedback and changes in their products and services, or if changes in the law so require. Changes to this statement will be made at Belcloud’s sole discretion. When they post changes to this Privacy Statement, Belcloud will revise the “recently changed” date in introduction of the statement above and describe the changes in the announcement which is also made available on their website. Belcloud encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to learn how it is protecting your data.

#### **HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have a privacy concern, complaint, or question for the Data Protection Officer of Belcloud, please contact the DPO by sending an email to admin[at]belcloud[dot]net. The DPO will respond to the questions or concerns within 5 business days.

Unless otherwise stated, Belcloud is a data controller for personal data it collects through the products and services it provides. Belcloud’s address is: Suite 9, Ansuya Estate, Revolution Avenue, Victoria, Seychelles. Email: admin[at]belcloud[dot]net.
